I'm sorry.
Forgive me...
for leaving.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS]
Why did you leave?
I was a coward.
When my parents discovered
our relationship,
they were furious.
They looked down on her.
They threatened me
and said something
terrible would happen
if I didn't leave her.
[SNIFFLES]
You know,
my mother...
she raised me all by herself.
Even when she's getting
more sick each day,
she never asked
anybody for help.
Because for her,
I was enough.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
This time,
let me fight for you.
I will do anything.
If you want
to save this hotel...
so be it.
Just give me...
another chance.
[MUSIC BECOMES GENTLE]
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOUTHING]
(In Filipino) I love you.
[MUSIC BECOMES ROMANTIC]